imshopping.com 2017-07-18

# IMshopping

This Privacy Policy of IMshopping, Inc. discloses the privacy policy and security practices related to the IMshopping Internet service (“Service”) and is hereby incorporated by reference into the <Terms of Service>. 

**Information Collected**

IMshopping may collect information from or about you when you use the Service, including your email address, username, password, bookmarks and associated content, conversations and messages, IP address, browser data, and cookies. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old. 

  * Email address, username and password are required for users to store and modify bookmarks and other content on the site.
  * Bookmarks, conversations and associated content are submitted by users and kept as private unless specifically designated to be public.
  * IP, browser and cookie data are utilized for the purpose of customizing the Service for each user.

You may request that we cease using and/or delete some or all of your information by changing your account settings or contacting Customer Service as indicated below. Additionally, we may from time to time provide you with the opportunity to “opt-in” and/or “opt-out” of receiving certain communications from us or our third party affiliates, and these settings can be changed at any by changing your account settings or contacting Customer Service as indicated below. You agree that such actions, including the deletion of your information and/or your election to opt-out of receiving certain communications, may impact your ability to fully use the Service. 

**Do Not Track**

We do not allow third parties to collect your personally identifiable information or track your actions through cookies and web beacons over time and across different websites or platforms.

In addition, you may be able to adjust your browser settings or other settings so that "do not track" requests are sent to the websites and mobile applications that you use. However, IMshopping will not disable tracking technology that may be active on this website in response to any "do not track" requests that are sent to the Service. 

**Customer Service**

If you choose to bookmark a page on IMshopping and save conversations in your local area, we will store the information you provide to us. IMshopping employees may examine this data on an individual user basis as necessary to operate the Service, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems. 

**Emails Sent To IMshopping**

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Service, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

**Use of Personal Information**

On an aggregate, non-personally identifiable level we may use data we collect from you to enhance the Service, analyze site usage, customize the site`s content, layout, and services and for other purposes that we may deem appropriate. These uses improve the Service and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Service. 

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services: 

  * IMshopping Community. Your User ID, bookmarks and any conversations or clips that you deem public are displayed throughout the Service. Therefore this data is available to the public. All of your activities on the Service will be identifiable to your User ID. Other people can see your bookmarks, conversations and clips, you have made public on the Service.
  * Legal Requests. IMshopping cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the IMshopping community from those doing harm. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your user information, including your user ID, email, bookmarks, and Service usage history, without notice to you.

If you are participating in the IMshopping service, we may send emails to you from time to time indicating updates to the IMshopping service and soliciting your feedback. If you do not wish to receive emails from IMshopping, you may indicate so within your account settings, to the extent available on the Service. 

**Use of Email and Address Book**

You may not use the Service to send spam or otherwise send content or communications that would violate our Terms of Service or applicable law. We may permanently store IM or email addresses sent from these tools for the purpose of simplifying future messages you wish to send. We do not read the content of these messages. 

If you send and messages using the service to an IM or email address that is not registered in our community, we do not use that IM or email address for any purpose other than to send your messages. We do not rent or sell these IM or email addresses. Other users may send messages to you via the IMshopping service. IMshopping does not review these messages before they are sent to you and IMshopping shall not be liable for their content. 

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by IMshopping. Please be aware that IMshopping is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of each site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through this Site. 

**Notice**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Service. All amended terms shall automatically be effective immediately and we are not required to notify you of the changes. 

**How can I manage my personal information or unsubscribe from emails?**

For e-newsletters, software updates notices, and special offers, you may unsubscribe from receiving IMshopping communications at [unsubscribe@imshopping.com](mailto:unsubscribe@imshopping.com). If you have created an account at IMshopping's website, you may change your personal information and account email alerts after logging into your account at [http://www.imshopping.com](http://www.imshopping.com/). 

**How can I contact IMshopping if I have any further questions?**

If you need help using the Service or have a question regarding the Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy, please contact Customer Service at [support@imshopping.com](mailto:support@imshopping.com). 

    IMshopping, Inc.
    4699 Old Ironsides Drive
    Suite 450
    Santa Clara, CA 95054
    408-228-4456 

Last updated as of January 22, 2016.
